Guide to the Stephen Mass Papers MSS.592
Fales Library and Special Collections
Stephen Mass Papers
1940-2019
1978-2009
Fales Library and Special Collections
Mass, Stephen
MSS.592
16.75 Linear Feet in 24 manuscript boxes, 3 half manuscript boxes, 2 small flat boxes, 2 oversize flat boxes, 1 media box, 1 oversize folder in shared housing, and 1 sound reel in shared housing.
33.92 Megabytes in 167 computer files.
1 sound tape reels
1 videocassettes (u-matic)
10 audiocassettes
6 film reels
Stephen Mass is an entrepreneur who co-founded the Mudd Club located at 77 White Street in downtown New York City in 1978 along with art curator Diego Cortez and Anya Phillips. The venue became a focal point of the downtown music, art, and cultural scene in the late 20th century, showcasing the intersections of popular and avant-garde performance culture, gender and sexuality, celebrity culture, music, visual art, fashion, film, and nightlife. The Stephen Mass Papers (inclusive dates 1940-2019, bulk dates 1978-2009) documents the founding and operation of the Mudd Club in New York City, Mass's other entrepreneurial ventures in New York, and his nightclubs and restaurants in Berlin, as well as his personal life and family history. Consisting of both paper and electronic formats, the collection includes extensive notebooks and notes containing the planning and working notes for Mass's various endeavors, financial and legal documents, promotional materials for events (such as posters, flyers, and newsletters), ephemera (differentiated from promotional material, as promotional material Mass collected from other clubs or organizations), press coverage, and photographic materials such as prints, negatives, and slides.
Arrangement
The Stephen Mass Papers is arranged into four series:
Series I. Mudd Club
Series II. Mudd Club Berlin
Series III. Other Enterprises
Series IV. Personal
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Stephen Mass in November 2019; the accession number associated with this gift is 2019.066.
Appraisal
During processing in 2021, out-of-scope materials were deaccessioned. These materials include roadmaps of Berlin and London, 1950s German ephemera, personal materials (passport, stamp book, and certificates) from other people, copies and originals of Mass's identification documents, payslips, empty CD and EP cases, and a phonodisc.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Fales Library and Special Collections, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596, with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Biographical Note
Stephen Mass is an entrepreneur who co-founded the Mudd Club located at 77 White Street in downtown New York City in 1978 along with art curator Diego Cortez and Anya Phillips. The venue became a focal point of the downtown music, art, and cultural scene in the late 20th century, showcasing the intersections of popular and avant-garde performance culture, gender and sexuality, celebrity culture, music, visual art, fashion, film, and nightlife. The Mudd Club closed in 1983, after which Mass embarked on other endeavors in New York and Berlin, such as founding Mudd Club Berlin in 2001, restaurant ownership, nonprofit work, teaching, and writing.
Scope and Contents
The Stephen Mass Papers (inclusive dates 1940-2019, bulk dates 1978-2009) documents the founding and operation of the Mudd Club in New York City, Mass's other entrepreneurial ventures in New York, and his nightclubs and restaurants in Berlin, as well as his personal life and family history. The bulk of the materials are dated 1978-2009, which is when the majority of these entrepreneurial ventures took place. The more inclusive dates of 1940 to 2019 include materials from his youth, retrospective articles, press, and ephemera regarding the Mudd Club, and manuscript drafts of his unpublished memoir.
Consisting of both paper and electronic formats, the collection includes extensive notebooks and notes containing the planning and working notes for Mass's various endeavors, financial and legal documents, promotional materials for events (such as posters, flyers, and newsletters), ephemera (differentiated from promotional material, as promo material Mass collected from other clubs or organizations), press coverage, and photographic materials such as prints, negatives, and slides. The majority of the collection pertains to the management and operation of the Mudd Club in New York City and the various nightclubs and restaurants that Mass owned and operated in Berlin, Germany, including the Mudd Club Berlin. The large number of photographic prints, negatives, and slides in the collection document Mass's work as a nightclub entrepreneur and photographer, with images documenting the condition of venue spaces (particularly in Berlin), parties and events (particularly at the Mudd Club), and images of his own personal travel and photographic subjects. The collection also includes handwritten notes, diary entries, and typescript manuscript drafts for Mass's unpublished memoir, and interview transcripts and correspondence with Tim Lawrence regarding the Mudd Club.
Nightclubs -- New York (State) -- New York.; Avant-garde (Aesthetics); Underground music -- New York (N.Y.); Nightclubs -- Berlin (Germany); Punk culture -- New York (State) -- New York; Business enterprises.; Restaurant management; Memoirs; Photographic prints.; Slides (photographs); Negatives (photographic); Notebooks; East village eye (New York, N.Y.); Fliers (printed matter); Clippings (information artifacts); Mass, Stephen
- Series I. Mudd Club, 1970-2019; 1979-1983; 8.75 Linear Feet in 11 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 2 small flat boxes, 2 oversize flat boxes, and 1 oversize folder in shared housing.
  Scope and Contents
  The Mudd Club series includes a large number of notebooks which contain planning and working notes. In particular are the annotated calendars spanning the years 1979 to 1983 which document the booking process for the nightclub and span the club's lifetime. Other notebooks created during the Mudd Club's operation include business notes, such as floor plans, diagrams, phone numbers, business cards, and other vendor information and coordination notes. This series contains a large number of photographic prints, negatives, and slides of parties and events at the Mudd Club, as well as slides and slide shows that were projected during events. Additional materials such as business plans and proposals, legal correspondence, check ledgers, and other financial records document the administrative side of the club's operation. There are also magazines, newspapers, and a limited run of the East Village Eye, which highlight the press coverage and publicity around the Mudd Club at the time. Promotional materials includes photographic and Xeroxed images, newspaper and magazine clippings, transparencies, and mockups and layouts of posters, newsletters, postcards, brochures, programs, invitations, or flyers. Membership cards, a guest book, a photo album, mailing lists and labels, and Rolodex contents document club attendees, vendors, and performers.
  This series also includes handwritten notes, outlines, diary entries, and typescript manuscript drafts for Mass's unpublished memoir, as well as competitive analysis and manuscript submission packets to publishers; interview transcripts and correspondence with Tim Lawrence; and a copy of The Riddle of Dr. Mudd. There are also audiovisual materials, such as audiocassettes and film and sound reels.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - 366 B'way, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annotated Calendars, Planning and Working Notes, 1979-1983 (Box 28, Folder 1-6)
  - Art Gallery, Keith Haring Drawing Show, 1981, 1997, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Business Cards, Art Exhibition Programs, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cale, John, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Labeled "1", circa 1970s-1990s (Box Shared Fales 045, Cassette 592_0008)
  - Cassette Labeled "Disney Tape, BAI", circa 1970s-1990s (Box Shared Fales 045, Cassette 592_0001)
  - Earth's Edge / Earth's End, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ephemera, Clit Club, circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Financial Records, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - Financial Records, Check Ledgers, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 9-13, Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Guest Book, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Legal Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Mailing Lists, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 4-8)
  - Mailing Lists, Alligator Girls, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Mailing Lists, Ball Gown Fashion, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Mailing Lists, Bowling, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mailing Lists, Celebrities, 1978-1980s (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Mailing Lists, Chao, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Mailing Lists, Clonetones, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Mailing Lists, Comedy, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mailing Lists, Full Hand List, 1982 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mailing Lists, General, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Mailing Lists, Robbe-Grillet, 1980 May 28 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Mailing Lists, GWIP, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 3-5)
  - Mailing Lists, Harry Abrams Alex Kayser List, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Mailing Lists, Howie Animal, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mailing Lists, Live, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Mailing Lists, Local Soho Artists and Non-Profit Curators, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Mailing Lists, Malanga, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Mailing Lists, Musuems, Galleries, Curators, Established Artists, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Mailing Lists, Music Industry, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mailing Lists, Outdated Music Industry, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Mailing Lists, Sur Rodney, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Mailing Lists, Talking Heads, Axel Comp, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Mailing Lists and Address Lists, 1980s, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Mailing List to Mudd Club, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Membership Lists, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Memoir Chapter Summaries, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Memoir Drafts, circa 1980s-1990s, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 20, Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Memoir Drafts and Notes, circa 1980s-2010s (Box 4, Folder 2-8, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_592_ER_1)
  - Memoir Mockup, circa 1980s-2010s (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Memoir Notes, circa 1980s-2010s (Box 4, Folder 10-13)
  - Memoir Notes and Diary Entries, 1988-1989, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 14, Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Memoir Notes and Outline, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Memoir Marketing, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Memoir, Simon and Schuster, 2016 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Memoir, St. Martin's Press, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Memoir, Wylie Agency, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Notebooks, Planning and Working Notes, 1977-1980s (Box 5, Folder 7-11, Box 28, Folder 7, Box 29, Folder 1-6, Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Notebooks, Planning and Working Notes for Arizona Nightclub, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Notebooks, Sabarsky Art Business Course, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Notebooks, Writing Notes on Mudd Club, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Notebooks, Writing Notes on Mudd Club and Haiti, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - New York Publicity Outlets, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Photo Album, 1982 December 25 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Photographic Print of Stephen Mass as Dr. Mudd, 1979 (Box Shared Fales 073, Folder 4)
  - Photographic Print, 1979-1983 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Photographic Prints, 1980-1985 (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
  - Photographic Prints, Anna Sui Pirate Fashion Show, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Photographic Prints, Inaugural Ball, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Photographic Prints, Mudd Anniversary, Berlin Move, King's Court Benefit, circa 1990s (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Photographic Prints, Mudd Reunion and King's Court Foundation, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Photographic Prints, R+Roll Funeral Ball, 1978-1983 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Photographic Prints, Sur Rodney Sur Film Screening, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Photographic Prints and Negatives, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 10-11)
  - Photographic Slides, 1978-1983 (Box 7, Folder 12-15, Box 8, Folder 1-16)
  - Photographic Slides (for Projection above Dance Floor), 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
  - Photographic Slides, Catholic School Girls Party, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Photographic Slides, Cocaine Cowboys, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Photographic Slides, Dance Floor Images, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Photographic Slides, Designered to Death, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Photographic Slides, Fashion, 1978-1983 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Photographic Slides, Helmut Newton, 1978, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Photographic Slides, IBM Anti-Trust Victory Celebration, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Photographic Slides, Mod London Miguel Osuna, 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Photographic Slides, Mudd Annex 254 E. 2nd St., 1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Photographic Slides, Milliners Fashion Show, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Photographic Slides, New Museum Party/Fundraiser, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Photographic Slides, Nigel Finch, "The Caravaggio Conspiracy," Mudd Club Scene, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Photographic Slides, Notables (Film, Literary, Music, Journalism), 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Photographic Slides, Slide Show, 1978-1983 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Photographic Slides, Slide Show S+M, 1978-1983 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Photographic Slides, SM Photos, Cale/Johnson Wedding, 1978-1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Photographic Slides, Terri Toy, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Photographic Slides, Victor Hugo, Various Persons, 1978-1983 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Photographic Slides, Woody Allen Wrap Party, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Photographic Slides, X-mas Office Party Parody, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Photographic Slides and Prints, Ball Gown Fashion Show, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Photographic Slides and Prints, Musicians (Carter, Perkins, Bertei), 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Photographic Slides and Prints, Soul Party, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Photographic Slides and Negatives, 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Press Coverage, 1979-2017 (Box 10, Folder 7-10, Box 11, Folder 1-3, Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Press Coverage and Research Files, 2013-2015 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Press Coverage, East Village Eye, 1981-1986 (Box 30, Folder 1-5, Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Promotional Materials, 1978-1983 (Box 10, Folder 2-5, Box 31, Folder 8-9)
  - Promotional Materials, Bowlmor, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - The Riddle of Dr. Mudd, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Rolodex, 1970s-1980s (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Tatyana Zareldyanskaya 3/7, circa 1970s-1990s (Box Shared Fales 045, Cassette 592_0003)
  - Tim Lawrence Interviews, Correspondence, Notes, 1999, 2013-2015 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Unlabeled Audiocassette, circa 1970s-1990s (Box Shared Fales 045, Cassette 592_0004)
  - Unlabeled Audiocassette, circa 1970s-1990s (Box Shared Fales 045, Cassette 592_0005)
  - Unlabeled Audiocassette, circa 1970s-1990s (Box Shared Fales 045, Cassette 592_0006)
  - Unlabeled Audiocassette, circa 1970s-1990s (Box Shared Fales 045, Cassette 592_0009)
  - Unlabeled Audiocassette, circa 1970s-1990s (Box Shared Fales 045, Cassette 592_0010)
  - Victor Bockris Master, circa 1970s-1990s (Box Shared Fales 046, Reel 592_0011)
  - Zinouy, circa 1970s-1990s (Box Shared Fales 045, Cassette 592_0002)
  - Zoya Gurevitch 3/7, circa 1970s-1990s (Box Shared Fales 045, Cassette 592_0007)
- Series II. Mudd Club Berlin, 1998-2016; 5 Linear Feet in 9 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 1 oversize folder.
  The majority of materials in this series are in German. Materials documenting the operations of the Mudd Club Berlin in 1999 and the 2000s include financial and legal documents; floor plans; correspondence; business proposals; planning and working notes in notebooks, notepads, and calendars; business cards; mailing lists; press coverage; two company stamps; and promotional materials. There are also photographic negatives and prints documenting the condition of venue spaces, with a smaller extent of material documenting parties and events. Much of the financial and legal documents pertain to loans, contracts, building applications, zoning, and noise complaints, among other issues. Some of these subjects also come up in the planning and working notes of the series, which also include research materials, inventories, diagrams, and payment notes.
  Materials are arranged alphabetically.
  - Administrative, Financial Documents, 2004-2009 (Box 12, Folder 1-4)
  - Administrative, Legal Documents, 2010-2011 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Administrative, Legal and Financial Documents, 2001-2015 (Box 12, Folder 6-8)
  - Annotated Calendars, Planning and Working Notes, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Business Cards, 1999-2016 (Box 12, Folder 9, Box 13, Folder 1-6)
  - Floor Plans and Planning Notes, 2004-2009 (Box 31, Folder 3, Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Mailing List, 1999-2016 (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
  - Mailing List, Art Forum Party, circa 1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Notebooks, Planning and Working Notes, 1999-2016 (Box 14, Folder 6-8, Box 15, Folder 1-7, Box 16, Folder 1-6)
  - Notebooks, Planning and Working Notes and Promotional Material, 2000-2005 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Notes and Ephemera, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Notes and Promotional Material, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Notes, Planning and Working Documents, 1998-2016 (Box 17, Folder 3-8, Box 18, Folder 1-4)
  - Notes, Promotional Material and Press Coverage, 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Notes, Techno Party, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Photographic Negatives, 1999-2016 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Photographic Prints, 1999-2007 (Box 18, Folder 8-10)
  - Photographic Prints and Negatives, 1999-2007 (Box 18, Folder 11, Box 19, Folder 1-6, Box 20, Folder 1-3)
  - Press Coverage, 2001, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Materials, 2000-2006 (Box 20, Folder 5-6, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_592_ER_3)
  - Promotional Materials and Notes, 2002-2004 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Materials and Press Coverage, 2000-2005 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Stamps, 1999-2016 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Strauss Social Planners Proposal, 2000 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_592_ER_2)
- Series III. Other Enterprises, 1987-2009; 1987-1993; 0.75 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box and 1 oversize folder.
  This series consists of notebooks, research files, correspondence, grant proposals and business plans which document Mass's restaurant planning, his work with Innovative Community Enterprises, and other nightclubs and businesses. The bulk of materials in Series III regard the planning of the restaurant at 77 Church Street that chef Bernard LeRoy and Mass began together, and notes include but are not limited to: diagrams, floor plans, photographic prints and negatives, catering schedules, calculations, budgets, equipment and supply notes, meeting notes, schedules, and recipes. Materials from Mass's time with Innovative Community Enterprises are primarily in electronic format, and include correspondence, reports, and meeting minutes.
  - Art Consulting, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Innovative Community Enterprises, 1993-1999 (Box 22, Folder 2, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_592_ER_4)
  - National Arts Club, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 3-4)
  - Restaurant, Bernard and Steve Church St, Stellan Holm Investor, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Restaurant Planning and Working Notes, 1989-1993 (Box 22, Folder 6-10)
  - Steve Mass Fine Photography Business Plan, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Technical Assistance Program Grant Proposal, 1998 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_592_ER_5)
  - UM Club, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 12-13)
  - UM Club Poster, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Series IV. Personal, 1940-2013; 1980-1989; 2.25 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes and 1 oversize folder.
  This series consists of personal correspondence, research files and manuscript drafts on Haiti after the overthrow of President Jean-Claude Duvalier, a Boy Scouts merit badge sash, a 1956 senior high yearbook, and photographic prints, negatives, and slides. The photographic prints, negatives, and slides document Mass's own personal trips to places like Lourdes, France; Barcelona, Spain; Miami Beach, Florida; and Newton Falls, Ohio, as well as photographic subjects of street scenes and people.
  - A.L. Miller Senior High School and Lanier Senior High School Yearbook, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Boy Scouts Merit Badge Sash, 1940s-1950s (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1987, 1999, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Haiti Manuscript Drafts, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Haiti Research Files, Photographic Prints, and Negatives, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Haiti Research Files and Manuscript Drafts, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Photographic Negatives, 1980s (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
  - Photographic Prints, 1980s (Box 23, Folder 9-10, Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Photographic Prints, Spain, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Photographic Prints and Negatives, 1980s (Box 24, Folder 2-8, Box 25, Folder 1-3)
  - Photographic Prints and Negatives, Lourdes, Barcelona, Rome, circa 1980s (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Photographic Prints and Negatives, Miami Beach, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Photographic Prints and Negatives, MTV, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Photographic Prints and Negatives, Newton Falls, Ohio Tornado, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Photographic Prints and Negatives, Spain, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Photographic Prints and Negatives, Victor Bockris, Legs MacNeil, Adam Saroyan, Jeff Goldberg, mid 1980s (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Photographic Prints and Negatives, 1980s (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - Photographic Prints and Negatives, Ephemera, 1940s-2000s (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Photographic Prints and Slides, 366 Broadway, Jamaica, Mexico, Mudd Grotto, 1979-1984 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Photographic Slides, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Photographic Slides, Art Show Clocktower Sweden, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Photographic Slides, Black River, 1981-1983 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Photographic Slides, Cape Kennedy, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Photographic Slides, Jamaica, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Photographic Slides, Jamaica, Chrissie, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Photographic Slides, Mignon, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Photographic Slides, Patrick AFB, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Research Files, Ethnographic Excursion, Barcelona, Lourdes, circa 1980s (Box 26, Folder 13)